回憶過往，生命的必經之途；
Remembrance, part of every life;
無數悔恨，時間如河水流淌。
num'rous regrets, the art of passing time.
終生難忘，焚膏繼晷的每夜；
Not one forgets, spent nights of chasing days;
兩眼闔上，所見已灰飛煙滅。
eternal rest, to witness being erased.
絕非尋常，以現今來講；
It is seldom seen in this world of now;
備受景仰，世間都一樣。
it is welcome, universe and out.
沒有陪伴，汝得隻身行；
It is seen, only from eyes of thine;
沒有代價？一切盡是命。
is it free? 'Tis only by invite.
回憶過往，生命的必經之途；
Remembrance, part of every life;
無數悔恨，時間如河水流淌。
num'rous regrets, the art of passing time.
終生難忘，焚膏繼晷的每夜；
Not one forgets, spent nights of chasing days;
兩眼闔上，所見已灰飛煙滅。
eternal rest, to witness being erased.
所見已灰飛煙滅。
To witness being erased.
如此沉重，迫切想看透未來，
It is ponderous, willing to know my fate,
如此漫長，早已等得不耐煩。
in its longest lingering while to wait.
我能看到，記憶被翻來覆去，
I can see, memory taken tolls,
我還需要，時間來接受離去。
I'm not ready, ready to let them go.
回憶過往，生命的必經之途；
Remembrance, part of every life;
無數悔恨，時間如河水流淌。
num'rous regrets, the art of passing time.
終生難忘，焚膏繼晷的每夜；
Not one forgets, spent nights of chasing days;
兩眼闔上，所見已灰飛煙滅。
eternal rest, to witness being erased.
回憶過往，生命的必經之途；
Remembrance, part of every life;
無數悔恨，時間如河水流淌。
num'rous regrets, the art of passing time.
時間如河水流淌...
The art of passing time...